Guide to the Historic Ephemera Collection 1880-2016
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Theater
  - Performance programs
    - "A Kiss for Cinderella." Programme. Theatre Royal, Haymarket.
    - "Merchant of Venice." Programme. Johnson high School. Johnson, WA. Circa 1922.
    - "The Seasons." Choral programme. Palouse, WA.
    - "Our Totem is the Raven." Poster. King Street Productions. Seattle. Circa 1960s.
    - "A Study Guide to the 16mm Sound Film Totems." Northern Films. Seattle 1962.
    - "The North American Indian." Movie booklet. Contemporary Films/McGraw Hill. Circa 1970.
    - "On Indian Land." Poster/order form. Gitksan-Wet'suwet'en Tribal Council. Hazelton, B.C., Canada. 1986.
    - "Spirit in the Earth." Pamphlet/order form. Circa 1960s.
  - Unsorted Items
- Transportation, Machinery
  - Jeep and Willys Jeep
    - "'Jeep' Planning." Pamphlet. Circa 1946.
    - "The Universal 'Jeep.'" Pamphlet. Circa 1946.
    - "Genuine Jeep Parts and Replacement Parts." Catalog No. 150. Circa 1940s.
- Travel (also see Places)
  - Airline
    - "Fly to Yellowstone." Brochure. United Air Lines.
    - "Northwest Airlines Souvenir Air Log." Brochure. 1939.
    - "Cascade Airways." System Timetable. 1978.
  - Automobile
    - "Highway 101 Map and Recommended Travel Stops," Golden State Motor Hotel (San Francisco). Circa 1970.
  - Bus
    - "Time Table Greyhound Service on Redwood and Pacific Highways." Brochure. 1939.
    - "Auto Interurban Lines." Spokane, Wash. 1937.
    - "Travel By Stage." Brochure- times tables. North Coast Lines. 1935.
    - "Washington Motor Coach System." Brochure and map. Washington Motor Coach System. 1934 (second issue).
  - Cruise Lines
    - Circle Line Covers the Waterfront. New York City. Circa 1968.
    - "The French Line wish you a 'Bon Voyage' on the 'France'." 1965 October.
    - "Vagabond Voyages Alaska." Brochure. Northland Transportation Company. Seattle, WA.
    - Passenger list and souvenir menus from an Alaska cruise. August 1929.
  - Railroads
    - "Low-Cost Fast Comfortable Travel in Union Pacific Coaches." Brochure.
    - "New Cascade Tunnel." Great Northern Railway. Circa 1930.
    - Go Pullman for "heart of town" convenience. Pamphlet. Pullman Company. Circa 1950s.
    - Sidetrack Newsletter. Inland Empire Railway Historical Society. 1995-1998 (9 issues).
    - Yardbull Newsletter. Inland Empire Railway Historical Society. 1990-1994 (11 issues).
    - Inland Empire Railroad Museum. Spokane Interstate Fairgrounds. Spokane, WA.
    - "Travel in Privacy in A Room of Your Own." Budd Railway Division. Brochure.
    - Placemats, Pacific Great Eastern Railway. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
    - The Snohomish Valley Railway Company. Bond. 1906. (Location note: in Oversize 2)
    - West Via the Scenic Route Across America. Pamphlet. Northern Pacific, Yellowstone Park Line.
  - Unsorted Items